Hello, I'm Hiker
CP Ida Shaw Pier.
The archway is scared.
Tomorrow is the day.
Once a year? Taiwan's toughest
one
-day Ironman
226km plus climbs Too much
talk the year before,
stopped (QQ)
This year... I've been preparing
for it. I'll challenge you again.
It's different this time.
We'll change the route
to Sun Moon Lake.
3.8KM back to this side,
follow it to T1 for changeover.
It's different this year.
Turn back near Dongpu.
I'm going back to Puli
to go west to Wuling,
and I'm running.
Swimming is easier than before,
biking and running relatively difficult routes
Not bad, it's quite representative
of Taiwan Sun Moon Lake is
the geographic center,
and Tatanga is a famous attraction.
Westbound to Wuling is another.
.. Very annoying route XDD
Changeover. Run,
run, run, run.
The floats are invisible,
and poor positioning can be
a real pain in the ass.
There's no line in the center. It's
gonna be foggy tomorrow. It's green,
it's green, it's green.
Just like the stock market (?).
（I'm in the mood to take
pictures before the game.)
（And watch people
talk to themselves.
(Than Santetsu puts up a photo
of climbing a volcano?
Championship ring! (I'm afraid
I won't be able to knock,
so I'll knock first)
(Pre
-match Briefing) Total
Climbing 6488M++.
(Swimming laps,
with only one green in the middle)
（The conference said to write
"fear" on it and burn it.)
At first I wrote swim to shore, and realized the
fear was: I couldn't swim to shore (so close...).
Write another 10? (Too much fear...)
Did you get it right? （My technician
couldn't stand it,
so he ripped it off and re
-glued it xD
VAAFO DARE Bikes,
same air bike, no breaks.
Flashlight Vision's latest RS45
wheelset with carbon fiber
The spokes are very light,
more than 1300g,
and the flywheel is replaced by a 36T.
The ceramicspeed BB is very
smooth and silky inside,
you can't see it.
I don't know if
it's a bad omen.
Number book All you have to take
UP capsules kplus aervana Helmet
I'll put this in the couple's tree.
And then they'll all do
their supply runs here,
because the cars are not
negotiable on Tatanga.
All the supplies at the
summit are over here,
so that means eight rides.
Running six portions front
first Windbreaker warm
wool BUFF COMPRESSPORT warm hat,
LeCol windbreaker
I'll get another can of
pectin water when I can.
Peak as a replacement Running charger
Flask Headlamp 2 Nitecore
COMPRESSPORT water belt
undershirt COMPRESSPORT
long
-sleeved iron coat can pee
CS compression full leggings (straight out of the
water) Hopefully the thighs will follow the
Compression of the calf can
be worn inside AKIWEI
Swimming Goggles Blue70
Long Sleeve Helix
Very thin (more relaxed) Long sleeves will
pull on the armpits and eat up the arms.
Seven packets for the ride to Tatanga and six packets for after Tatanga,
all filled.
I finished the first
jar in four hours.
Lemon plums are good with anything.
（I'd like to have a meeting
with you all to talk about it.
（The one who knows the
situation best is Mr.
Nanny Kamm.
People asked me if I hadn't
just fallen off the bike,
and I said it was more than that.
He flashed his back the other day,
and the runners didn't eat much.
(I'm afraid I won't be able to use it hahaha) The
chairs have been put away so I can't sit on them.
No sitting this year!!! I'm stepping
on it! What's the latest one?
What's this? XD OneOneOneOne This is
the lightest 23g it's ever gonna be.
There are TWO (????)
And THREE(?????
Remember to cheer up tomorrow,
0400 the next day (tattoo stickers
never go on well).
（You didn't sleep?
(I'm super sleepy .......) This year,
we have a visually impaired player,
Hsing, who is very strong.
（Which one is the foot
punch?) Stop it.
Stop rinsing your feet.
～～～～ (Don't you have to wash your feet?)
（You're not coming to be
a ghost of Sun Moon Lake?
（What's that smell? No
one's spraying outside,
asshole.
Can't suck it in (the outside
of the spray is slippery!)
He's peeing.
That's gross.
Last one out of T1,
please help CP with the tips.
Pissed all over the floor,
not a drop. It's all over me (？？？？).
My youngest toothy cheerleader (he'll be
in the womb in 2023 when FXT is on).
（Thinking about how I'm gonna swim.
Go to the SUP position
and wait for the gun.
（"Back to the VIP
room for the team.
" "Wait here for about 75 minutes.
Seems like it.
- No,
it doesn't.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
90 minutes to go! 90 (I'm not talking
shit anymore guys :))))))
T1 finished at 2:08!!!!
I was so scared
I thought I was going back to Taipei!
I was filming someone and kept
calling out to Li Qibin,
but he ignored me. Then Li Qibin...
It just drifted over from here,
nothing happened. It was the same two years ago (haha).
(Because the first section of the Huan Tan Road is narrow,
the supply vehicle has to rush to catch up with the runners)
I chased after the large jar of purple
ointment and coconut water allergy
medication on the first stretch of flat road,
trying to save time.
You absolutely must
stop at the slowest
Aiyu Bridge (＊＆＾％＄)
Xinyi Township is so beautiful~~
How are you?
I'll ask Agan to help me wipe
it later (specifically!).
(If the last supply point isn't at the control station,
stopping at Aiyu Bridge is the best option.)
Let me introduce the scale
of the elite players.
The elite players are
those we will have.
We sat in the driver's seat
and then the passenger seat.
There was a photo being
taken over there,
and then an editor posted it in the background,
plus another...
We, the supply crew,
just drove around taking pictures, then uploaded
them and posted them online.
The supply crew got out of the vehicle.
"Apply,
smear, eat" Hakka
CP Our organization is
We're going to have lunch
and take a nap now,
and then wake up at 12 o'clock
to check on that.
With the location point,
we can decide which way to go (we
arrived at Aiyu Bridge smoothly).
Banana (I planned to eat a solid
one before going up the mountain)
Quickly change your gear at
the top of the mountain
We had plenty of time,
so we successfully extended our lives.
I'm now eligible to continue
playing the game at noon (????)
Wow (everyone's so happy haha)
Rice is falling (my rice ball)
Smoothly 50 minutes downhill from the mountaintop
- purple ointment
purple ointment purple ointment
I've been holding
my pee for 5 hours...
(Because urinating for a long time can
also replenish your energy, haha)
Did you pee too far? Are you alright?
Are you feeling okay?
You can stop along the way,
and finally stop in the water.
Bye
-bye (the headwind on the way
back was really tough to ride).
Do you want me to water
it? I want to water it.
I want to get in the car,
can you help me remove
the headlights?
Three EVE pills for
menstrual cramps?
Lei (4 brownish
-white capsules): What would you like to drink? Soft water,
or plum blossom wine? (Both
are plum wines...)
If you're not here,
could you please change
the water for me?
Help me remove the light.
We don't have ice.
(Choose "We don't have ice")
Give me a banana at the highest
point facing the sun (I always
arrange for solid foods to
be eaten at higher points).
Ice cubes~~~ Here's
a banana for you
180 (The supply officer
first prepares
and checks the running gear)
(Blood pressure measurement)
T2 completed
in 4 minutes and 27 seconds
(Almost got hit,
haha) Wait a minute,
okay? Why did you sit down?
(I'm very tired right now) I'll
try to get to 17K by 6:00.
You can proceed steadily.
Do you have cramps? It's so far,
I ran a long way down.
I was wondering why it took you
so long; I thought I'd
see you after running
just a short distance.
None of the results
were seen.
You felt the same way
in Nepal back then,
very uncomfortable at first, then...
Take a rest. If you really can't go on,
just say so.
It's okay (I felt
a lot of pressure
while everyone was waiting).
Everyone says if you
can't swim up,
just go up and show them we've
already prepared a running test.
The preparations of the Hehuan Master
(I just went down) – I didn't
see anyone at all, then I saw someone like this,
and then I said…
What do you want? (Don't
go to the wrong place,
okay?)
(Handsome guy~~)
(Running away~~)
(Run!) This angle is so cool,
I have to run! (Damn,
it's super steep...)
(It's too early,
the scenery here isn't that beautiful yet.
) You're so amazing! (So encouraging! QQ)
(Is it okay? Is it okay,
handsome?) Absolutely hilarious! Hahahaha!
Why do I need to come
up after swimming?
You look great XD (??
I was just thinking
of giving up when I was at 3K)
As a result,
I don't know why it held up.
I want to come up and show
him (Brother Xiu)!
Everyone keeps saying we can't
stop! Anyone coming up from
behind in the swimming group? (You're
the second to last.)
MDFK!!
The last one, right? He rode
up on his bike and told me...
We're the last two,
there are 45 people running now,
but I don't know where you are.
Climbing the main peak will be cold
(I just came down from there).
Dog! Now the running
buddy thinks...
No need to run (???)
(Feeling pessimistic)
Let's cheer each other on! What
do you want to say to Tiger?
He's not constipated? (He felt
a little better after nightfall,
but was still very tired.)
(7
-Eleven store in Cingjing,
20K) Have a good meal!
Eat only when you're
sure it's safe to
eat (be careful here before
you go for a run).
(For example,
if the plan is to allocate 20K for instant
noodles) Don't play with dogs!!
(Wearing the arm sleeves that Coach Yan Qing,
a national team player, gave me for support)
(Unwashed???)
Is it tasty?
Add some vegetables
(vegetable stems??).
He's still short of 10
seconds and 20 seconds.
So many (rushing around!)
are dying.
Are you confident about the last 2.
3K (to Yuanfeng)?
Yes, yes, yes, yes (the supply officer
asks and answers himself, haha).
How are you? (Full of energy, haha)
Not good? You look pretty good,
look how well you pulled through!
I prefer white T
-shirts (I didn't finish getting the white shirt).
Black T
-shirts (black shirts) won't get dirty easily; white T-shirts get dirty easily.
A white T
-shirt can be worn
as pajamas XDDDD 10:30
Now it's 9.5 to
10 minutes a minute,
that's plenty of time! (The official statement: 13 seconds
off in swimming speed. The whole world knows now, lol)
It's 9:07 now. What time is it here?
9 o'clock! Time management master.
You have so much footage today,
there's no reason not to edit it (Mur wasn't
going to edit videos anymore, haha).
How are you feeling? Be careful!
(One to ten minutes)
How much pain? Nine
out of ten!
Just one point left, time to reach the summit! (Seriously,
what a smooth talker!)
Ring the bell again at 12 o'clock
(last 2km of mountain road).
It's relatively
easy to travel (?).
Is Taiping the place?
How are you feeling? Jenny wants you
to do something (three small things).
She said you have a lot of ideas and told
me to think about them (preferably now).
(How confident were you about
the evening match last night?)
I'm not confident (how confident
were I before going into the water?)
Do you know what the most difficult thing
is when you start from the water?
(Standing swim) I almost drowned,
I swallowed a ton of water.
(Shouldn't we go hiking?) (If
we don't go hiking soon,
we'll lose followers.)
Seriously, nobody watches these
videos anymore QQ (Anyway,
we chatted and laughed all
the way down the mountain)
(The next day,
the awards ceremony) (A
slightly sunken face)
(Thank you Jovi, the organizer,
for putting on such an exceptional competition.)
(Still want to show off
a little) That's
all for today's video!
If you like my videos,
welcome to Hiker CP!
What happens next? (*&^%^&*(
See you on the mountain next time,
everyone...)
Extreme Ironman,
log out! Coconut Water
Run!! Seriously? We really
have to run? I thought...
Everyone can go home
now :) 100% sure!
(Okay) (The supply clerk is starting
to get used to it, haha)
Okay (the part in the water
was the most painful)
My plan was to follow others
(which I myself find absurd).
This is very sticky and
easily sticks crookedly.
Both are Madform purple ointment; I'll use small
jars to portion them out for easier carrying.
(Huh, what are we going to do??)
They have no chemistry.
(Forgot what he was going to
say after a pause) I'll
definitely come up! (Swearing
confidently)
(Will it come to this?) (Nods
in satisfaction >///<)
Likes and dislikes
(What a jinx!!)
(The Great Demon King swims
up Sun Moon Lake)